musingsfromasahm.com 2013-12-28

# Giveaway Rules, Disclosure & Privacy Policy, & Copyright - Musings From a Stay At Home Mom

**Giveaway Rules:**

If you enter a giveaway here at Musings From a Stay At Home Mom, you are agreeing to abide by these rules:

  * Entry is through Rafflecopter, unless otherwise noted. Commenting does not enter you.
  * Winners are chosen by Random.org and will be emailed. The winner will have 48 hours to respond. If a winner does not, a new winner will be chosen and the first winner will lose the right to their prize.
  * Winners will be listed on the [Winners ](http://musingsfromasahm.com/winners/)page &/or on the giveaway page on the Rafflecopter form.
  * Please allow up to 6 weeks to receive your prize. If you do not receive your prize after that, let us know and we will check with the sponsor.
  * If a sponsor fails to send a prize, we cannot be held responsible.
  * By entering a contest, you agree to release Musings From a Stay At Home Mom and all associated parties of any liability.

**Disclosure Policy:**

This is my personal blog, written and edited by me. I write about what I love, what I find interesting, and what is relevant for my family.

You may see ads on my sidebar. I may receive monetary compensation or they may have an affiliate link, meaning I may receive some money or a discount if you click on it, and/or buy something. There also may be affiliate links throughout some of my posts. I do receive monetary compensation; it helps fund this blog!

We (myself and the review team) do receive free products to keep from companies in exchange for a review. We’ll always tell you in a post if something was sent to us for free. We’ll always give you our honest opinion – they’re not buying us off!

I also do sponsored posts. These are noted at the beginning of each post and mean that I received monetary compensation for sharing the information. I still only share my own opinion!

**Copyright:**

Please do not save, copy and paste to your blog or website, or use any of our personal images or photos. All pictures are the property of Musings From a Stay At Home Mom.

**Here’s the more official terms:**

This policy is valid from 14 May 2011

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post may not always be identified as paid or sponsored content.

In accordance with recent FTC regulations, we are hereby notifying you that some or all of the links contained herein on this domain could result in the payment of an affiliate commission to the owner of this blog. If you see a link, you should assume that it may result in the owner of this blog earning some money.

In addition to other companies, musingssahm.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

**Privacy Policy:**

Your privacy is important to us. We never sell or give out your information, including your email address, except for the occasion that you may win a prize that requires you be contacted (ie an e-gift certificate.) If you win a giveaway, your address is only provided to the sponsor for the purpose of shipping prizes.

We do not share personal information with third-parties nor do we store information we collect about your visit to this blog for use other than to analyze content performance through the use of cookies, which you can turn off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. We are not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this blog on other Web sites or media without our permission. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.  

If you have any questions regarding these policies, please contact Erika at Musingsfromasahm(at) gmail(dot)com.
